var data = [
  {
    "category": "Lower",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<h1>Camping</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Lowest if you camp with your household contacts.</h2><br><ul><li>Plan well to avoid unanticipated stops and interactions.</li><li>Respect the community and follow local guidelines and restrictions.</li><li><a href='https://covid19.colorado.gov/safer-at-home/guidance-by-sector/campgrounds'>Campground guidance</a></li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<h1>Outdoor exercise and recreation</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Outdoor activity is generally lower risk.<h2><br> <ul><li> Passing by people briefly is lower risk.</li><li>The more people the greater the risk.</li><li>Try to find less crowded areas and times.</li></ul"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<h1>Vacation home, hotel or motel</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Once you are in the lodging, the risk is lower.</h2><br><ul><li>Car travel with household members is lowest risk.</li><li>Try to plan ahead and take the necessary food and supplies.</li><li>Think about what you will do if you become ill while you are away.</li><li>Do a personal risk/benefit analysis for activities you might participate in while away.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<h1>Recreational sports</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>It depends on the sport and the practices. </h2> <br> <ul><li>Outdoor singles tennis could be lower risk.</li> <li>Modify rules to avoid contact, and wash hands and use disinfectant on equipment.</li><li>Involve close contact with others so there is some additional risk.</li></ul>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Medium",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<h1>Shopping</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Depends on whether the shopping is indoors or outdoors. It can, and sometimes hard to maintain distance. Others may not wear masks</h2><br><ul><li>Go with a list, and take advantage of less-crowded hours.</li><li>Stores often offer hours for higher-risk individuals and have guidelines to follow.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<h1>Dining out</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>To reduce risk, dine outside.</li><li>Donâ€™t linger or mingle with other parties.</li><li>wear your mask if you need to get up to use the restroom and when coming and going.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<h1>Playground</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>Outside, but difficult to maintain physical distance between children and surfaces are frequently touched.</li><li>Be kind and wait for your turn.</li><li>Take disinfecting and hand cleaning supplies with you.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<h1>Swimming</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>Strategize ways to avoid common areas and maintain distance.</li><li>Wear a mask when possible and bring an extra mask in case one gets wet.</li></ul>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Higher",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<h1>Airline travel</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>Check airlines and airports for their policies and procedures about COVID-19.</li><li>Check restrictions in the place you are traveling to.</li><li>Prepare well with enough medication to last the entire trip, plus extra in case the trip must be extended.</li><li>Bring hand sanitizer and disinfecting wipes.</li><li>Consider what you would do if you became ill while you are away.</li><li>The risk may increase as more people become comfortable traveling.</li><li>Check policies about canceling due to crowded flights where social distancing is not possible.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<h1>Places of worship</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>Places of worship should follow guidelines; this will help minimize risk.</li><li>People in higher-risk categories should carefully consider whether alternatives that are not in-person would be better.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<h1>Personal services</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>Use personal service providers who follow guidelines.</li><li>Limit talking -- when someone is infected, talking results in more virus particles in the air.</li><li>Higher-risk individuals should consider carefully.</li></ul>"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<h1>Events and gatherings</h1>",
        "answer": "<ul><li>Smaller and in-person gathering in which individuals from different households remain spaced at least 6 feet apart, wear masks, do not share objects</li><li>Medium-sized in-person gatherings that are adapted to allow individuals to remain spaced at least 6 feet apart and with attendees coming from outside the local area.</li></ul>"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Highest",
    "questions": [
      {
        "points": 100,
        "question": "<h1>Bars, breweries, nightclubs</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Minimize time and stay outdoors. where you might be able to maintain distance.</h3><br><h3>Avoid crowded locations</h2><br><h2>People in high-risk categories should consider higher risk activities carefully.</h2>"
      },
      {
        "points": 200,
        "question": "<h1>Gym, fitness facility</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Higher-risk people should consider safer alternatives, such as outdoor or home exercise.</h2>"
      },
      {
        "points": 300,
        "question": "<h1>Singing with groups</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>Singing has been shown to result in more virus particles in the air at distances much greater than 6 feet.</h2>"
      },
      {
        "points": 400,
        "question": "<h1>Large Gatherings</h1>",
        "answer": "<h2>PLEASE KINDLY AVOID, Save yourself your family and save everyone of us from this deadly pandemic</h2>"
      }
    ]
  }
];
